pdf2go.com 2016-11-19

# Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

### 1\. Collection of Personal Information

When visiting pdf2go.com, the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

### 2\. Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART Cookie

Google, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet. To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL: http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html . Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google’s own privacy policies. Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies, picture upload has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers.

### 3\. Links to third party Websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

### 4\. Collecting e-mail Addresses

Users have the possibility to enter their e-mail address for various functions. pdf2go.com does not rent, sell, or share your personal information or email address with any other companies.

### 5\. Certain Exceptional Disclosures

We may disclose your information if necessary to protect our legal rights or if the information relates to actual or threatened harmful conduct or potential threats to the physical safety of any person. Disclosure may be required by law or if we receive legal process.

### 6\. Storage of User Files

When users upload files to be edited or converted, pdf2go.com stores those files on its servers. The files remain in place on the servers for users to download, until they have been downloaded 10 times. All files will also be deleted 24 hours after conversion. There is no backup made of user files, neither are the contents of the files monitored without permission of the uploader.

### 7\. Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

### 8\. Cookies and Web Beacons

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. We also use third party advertisements on pdf2go.com. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited.
